Easton!
-[crowd chanting] Easton! Easton! Easton!
-[man] Let's go!
-[chanting continues]
-[ominous music playing]
[whirring]
[chanting continues]
Easton! Easton! Easton!
["Doing It for the Country"
by Vincent's Last Summer playing]
[Teagan giggling]
There's nothing hotter
than the smell of bleach. [laughing]
Less talking.
[movement in other room]
-Maybe we should go somewhere else.
-Yeah.
♪ I'm doing it for the country ♪
♪ Just give me one more reason ♪
♪ Call it hate, but you call it treason ♪
♪ There only is one demon ♪
♪ Can't do bunker drills, can't afford ♪
-♪Just give me one more reason ♪
-[phone beeping]
-[music stops]
-You gotta be kidding me.
-Five more minutes.
-No, okay?
-There's a regatta in two hours.
-What?
The team's gonna be here soon.
I'll leave first in case anyone's outside.
Okay.
Wait. I think you have something… there.
[music starts again]
♪ Everywhere I go
I see your face up on billboards now ♪
♪ I'm gonna take it all
A privatized free-for-all ♪
♪ I had to get a train and it was
An hour and a half delayed now ♪
♪ I think my time is up
Occupation ending, give it up now ♪
[sighs]
And here we go.
♪ I do it all for you ♪
Mad, wanna help me bring this stuff in?
Okay, but you owe me.
I put a roof over your head,
provide you
with unlimited high-top Chucks.
-But we ain't even yet?
-Close, but not yet.
I'll keep that in mind.
-Hey.
-Oh, hey.
-How are you feeling about today?
-Yeah. I like our chances.
What, uh, happened with you and Teagan?
I didn't see you guys
at the end of the dance. Did it go well?
No. It's not happening.
Here. Let me help you.
Here, I'll take this.
-Do you want to talk about it?
-Uh…
No, I don't. It's not gonna work.
Okay, it's fine.
[Madison] Wait, why is the truck for sale?
Is something going on?
[quiet, somber music playing]
The shop's in trouble.
Dad laid off the other mechanics,
and I've been picking up the slack.
That's tough.
Is there anything I can do?
I just… I gotta get through this.
-Okay.
-[object crunching]
[Madison gasps] Oh, oh no!
I'm so sorry.
Don't worry, it's fine. It's okay.
["Hold Me Close"
by Russell Chimes playing]
-[Noah] Prepare yourselves for tonight.
-There gonna be a DJ?
I heard Diplo came last year.
Two years ago,
we took the yacht to Deer Island.
-Partied on the beach all night.
-Sweet!
[Teagan] Hey!
-Yo. Smoothie up.
-Thanks.
You guys talking about
the regatta after-party?
Hell yeah!
Noah's planning it this year,
and he has a lot to live up to.
[Noah] You will not
be disappointed, friends.
Hey. Morning, boys.
-[team] Morning.
-[Josh exhales]
Morning, Teagan.
Josh. Sip-sip.
Hey!
[Richard] Josh.
Dad.
I thought you were supposed to be
with Mom and Granddad.
They're looking for
a good spot to watch from.
Son.
I have some hard news.
Dad promoted Karina
to President of Luxury Travel.
Wasn't that was supposed to be your job?
Yeah.
She scooped me.
That's not good.
I need a win here, Josh.
[foreboding music playing]
You're in stroke.
A win will put us
back on top in Dad's mind.
Right.
I'd, uh, better go join him.
[tense music playing]
[exhales]
Morning.
Coach asked for the slow cooker.
I left it on the counter.
-Okay. Thanks.
-Yeah.
Is there, uh… anything else
you wanna talk about?
Yo.
No.
One whole word.
Still more communicative than your texts.
Mm.
[Perry whispering] Something's going on.
Cam.
I know you had a hard time at the dance,
and I am trying to give you your space,
but you know you could talk to me.
Yeah, I know.
Thanks.
[sighs]
-Go on.
-Okay.
[intriguing music playing]
Hey, girl. You and Cam
didn't come to the after-party.
Now the vibe's all formal. What's up?
You guys trying to sneak around,
keep things profesh?
No comment.
So… yes?
Okay. Good chat.
-[Noah] So?
-She gave me nothing.
-Dude.
-[Perry] Yeah.
[Hayden] All right, crew, huddle up.
Bring it in, bring it in.
Last regatta before the Haverford Cup.
If we place here, we can secure our spot,
giving us a shot at the podium.
The first time in ten years.
[team cheering and exclaiming]
Y'all feel good about that? You should!
Because this race is yours for the taking.
Yeah, Westvale is toast!
No, wait. They are past toast.
They are ash. They're…
-Um…
-Tephra.
What the hell is a tephra?
-Material produced by volcanic eruption.
-Isn't that just lava?
Okay, losing the plot here.
-Coach?
-Thank you.
Listen, a hot streak is great.
But Westvale's gonna do
whatever it takes to get back on top.
So one clean drive after another,
and we can take this thing, yeah?
[team] Yes, Coach!
All right. Regis?
[both] Yeah?
I meant Josh.
Let's take it out easy today, okay?
It's a head race, not a sprint.
You got it?
Yes, Coach.
[Hayden] Okay.
Go change,
do whatever prep you need to do,
and I will see you
out on the tarmac in 60.
Let's get to work.
-[Teagan] Great.
-And just a quick remindy about the party.
It's gonna be both the bee's knees
and the cat's meow.
I'm getting a bad feeling
about this party.
Me too, man.
I'm allergic to bees and cats.
[phone buzzing]
[Teagan] Remember,
back your blades in at the catch.
Okay! Let's go!
[team assenting]
[buzzing continues]
Hi.
[Logan] I'm here a little early.
I'll see you in five.
Hey.
Congrats on being back in stroke.
Thanks for your support.
Must be a lot of pressure though.
And why's that?
'Cause when I was in stroke, we won.
[tense music playing]
Don't screw it up.
[crowd cheering and whooping]
Yo. Sunglasses are broken.
Yeah, taped them up.
It's regulation.
The whole team has to wear the same thing.
-Yours can't be broken.
-What do you want me to do?
You don't have a backup?
Not all of us have an extra
$300 lying around, jackass.
Okay.
But you can't go out like that.
We won't match.
Then we won't match.
Fine.
I'll tell the whole team
that we're all going without sunglasses.
Yo, you think you deserve to be in stroke.
You don't.
Excuse me?
I have better technique than you.
I'm faster than you. I'm just better.
Hey. Coach picked me.
I have been working my ass off.
I absolutely deserve to be in that seat.
No, you don't. You were born lucky.
And you need to figure that out.
Maybe everything you have,
you don't deserve.
[dramatic music playing]
[crowd chanting] Easton! Easton! Easton!
Easton! Easton! Easton!
-[chanting continues in background]
-[Teagan laughs]
-Thank you.
-All right!
Everybody here?
Coxie, count us in.
All right.
Easton on three!
-[all] One, two, Easton!
-Let's go!
Crew, go get your boat.
[Teagan] Go!
[tense music playing]
[woman on PA] Easton Prep, on standby.
Back in the saddle.
Feeling good?
Let's do this.
Paddle up.
[woman] Easton Prep, on the paddle.
[Teagan] Legs!
Starting off strong! Here we go!
-Easton, go!
-[horn blows]
And pull! Let's go, Eagles! Come on!
Starting strong! Pull!
[fast-paced music playing]
Keep it up! Keep it up!
Go! Legs! Pull!
-Oh!
-[team exclaiming]
It went off.
-[Cam] What?
-[Crabcatcher] What was that?
[Ryder] What's going on?
-My oar!
-[Noah] Guys!
It just snapped.
[Quaid] No way!
-[Josh groans]
-[sighing]
[Lana] Easton Prep, you are disqualified.
God!
[somber music playing]
[Hayden] Okay, guys.
I know this is not
how we wanted this to end.
But sometimes, it's just not your day.
But we should have had that race.
We still have a chance.
We're disqualified from the race,
but not from making the Haverford Cup.
If Cedarside and Lakeview
don't place in the top three,
we'll still qualify.
We just have to wait for the results
for the other teams to come in. Okay?
Have a good time tonight.
You've earned it. Keep your head up.
Man, if our oar didn't break,
we could've been on that podium.
It was a fluke. It happens.
[Noah] You know what else happens?
-Our after-party.
-[team] Yeah!
[clapping]
-[Ryder] Who's the musical guest?
-[Perry] Shit. Are we seeing Bad Bunny?
Indeed, we will be in the proximity
of something very bad.
-Hey!
-Yeah, let's get bad, baby.
And here it is. Our night's marquee event…
a murder mystery.
-Uh-oh.
-Oh, hell no.
Why?
Our tale begins in an era
marked by greed and rebellion.
America's moral compass,
once steady, now spins recklessly.
I bring you all…
to the Roaring '20s!
Now, we've all read The Great Gatsby.
[all] We did?
We did. It was on last year's curriculum.
Okay, well, Crabby and I
have read The Great Gatsby.
Now, during Prohibition,
alcohol was forbidden.
Is this a dry party?
Yeah, obviously.
-[team moaning]
-Oh, no.
[stammers] But the Roaring '20s
gave birth to jazz.
-And cabaret.
-Yeah.
Ugh.
-A friggin' murder mystery.
-[Baloo] A dry murder mystery.
Why do you hate us, Noah?
[Teagan] Guys, come on.
Noah spent a lot of time
planning this party, so… go ahead.
[clears throat]
-[dramatic music playing]
-A heinous crime occurred
-in this opulent mansion.
-[crunching]
-[music stops]
-Quaid, not right now.
What?
Okay.
-[music restarts]
-A heinous crime occurred
inside this opulent mansion.
The murder of a reclusive dowager duchess.
The weapon? An oyster shucker.
The motive? Her priceless ruby necklace.
Stolen.
Now, you'll all find your characters
and costumes by your changeroom cubbies.
Disperse!
-Ah!
-[music stops]
Boys, come on. Let's… disperse! Disperse!
Let's stop waiting for the results
and go solve a murder!
It's gonna be great!
[team grumbling]
-I'm sure.
-[grumbling continues]
[Quaid] That makes a lot of sense.
I worked really hard on this.
It's gonna be fun.
-[grumbling continues]
-[Noah laughs awkwardly]
Yes.
Hey, Dad. Uh, trying you again
'cause I haven't heard back from you.
I, uh…
I know the race
didn't go the way we needed.
I'm sorry that I let you down.
[somber music playing]
[sighs]
Well, I'll be…
[mysterious string music playing]
Who in this dastardly rogues' gallery
is responsible for the slaying
of the innocent dowager?
I've hidden clues all around this mansion
that you and your fellow suspects
must gather.
Announce yourselves!
Guys, come on.
"I'm Carl."
"A speakeasy steward
with dreams of a better life."
-Wait, I'm a janitor?
-Ooh, with a selfless heart.
Or one filled with bloodlust.
"I am Eleanor Ramshine.
A wealthy flapper who is…
judgy and into hats."
-What a typecast.
-[Noah] Yes!
You two will begin in the kitchen
after a clandestine necking party.
-Necking?
-Wait, what's necking?
"Baloo and I are big sluggers."
"Two mobster henchmen
to one of Chicago's unfinest."
[imitating gangster]
We're gonna break your legs!
Speedy Sinclair. Newspaper boy.
-Amelia Faye. Silent film star.
-[Teagan clears throat]
You're with…
Mr. Brandenburg, a federal agent.
You two will begin in the boat sheds.
And last but not least…
Oil magnate Edward Harold.
Who is also…
-[glass clattering]
-…a secret moonshine brewer.
[team]
-Yeah!
-Wait up, Quaid, that is not on your card.
Yeah, the speakeasy is open for business.
I got one for each of you. Come here.
This is mine. Don't take it.
[Noah] Quaid,
where did you even get these? Stop.
This is my emergency stash.
[Baloo laughing mischievously]
Okay, uh, uh, guys,
just don't forget about the clues, okay?
There's gonna be a new discovery
in round two!
[rower] Yeah!
[in fake English accent] Okay,
Mr. Brandenburg. What's the clue again?
Well, let's see, Amelia Faye.
[Teagan laughs]
"A shining three is where you'll find me."
Hey, Noah sits in the three seat.
Maybe our next clue
is in one of the shells.
[Teagan laughing]
Yes.
Ah.
Bad break.
Yeah.
-[Josh sighs]
-Did your dad call you back yet?
No.
And I don't think
he's going to anytime soon.
Hey. Josh, come on.
There's nothing you could have done, okay?
Don't beat yourself up.
We'll get 'em next time.
Okay.
Huh.
Wait a second.
What?
-That didn't just break on its own.
-[sinister music playing]
That's sawed through.
What?
[Teagan] The oar was sabotaged.
Look. It was cut part way through
so it'd break during the race.
-Shit.
-Who would do this?
-You can't be serious.
-We've stumbled upon a real mystery.
It was cut with an electric saw.
It's pretty common. Every team has one.
-Well, why the hell would someone do this?
-[Ryder] Well, isn't it obvious?
Some Westvale scumbag is probably
trying to keep us off the podium.
-Yeah.
There's no way they could've done that.
Our oars were in sight during the regatta,
so someone must have cut it before,
while it was still in the boat shed.
But you need a key card to get in.
And we're the only ones
who have key cards.
So that means it was one of us.
All right, who the hell did this?
Show yourself, you traitor.
Busted our asses all season.
-I can't believe one of you did this.
-It wasn't you?
-Why would I do it?
-Why would any of us?
[all arguing]
Everybody calm down. Calm down.
Guys, we can't let this break us apart.
All right? There has to be a team
at the end of this.
Noah and I are gonna figure this out.
-Okay?
-[mysterious music playing]
-[Noah] We need to narrow our time frame.
-Mm-hmm.
We were all in the boatshed this morning
between 7:30 and 8:30 a.m.
So the sabotage must have happened
after that. Between 8:30 and 9:30.
Right, so where was everyone this morning?
Uh, I was outside stretching with Noah.
Me and Crabby were taking selfies
in the erg room.
-I was doing my pre-race meditation.
-Why are we checking alibis?
None of us wanted to lose this race.
There's no motive here.
On the surface, dear Crabby.
So we need to look for the motive
underneath the motive.
What the hell does that mean?
It means, Perry,
we all have our pre-race superstitions.
Our "free speed," so to speak.
Crabby eats pasta.
Baloo does karaoke
when he thinks no one's watching.
-I do not.
-Josh chooses the oar with the pink tape.
So the question we should be asking
isn't, "Who would target the team?"
But, "Who would target…
Josh?"
[tense music playing]
So… someone on the team was targeting me.
Why?
Who?
Oh, come on.
It could've been Baloo.
He's pissed at Josh
'cause he dumped his sister.
Yeah. Should've heard him ranting
about Josh and Britney last night.
-Perry.
-Sorry, Baloo.
You broke up with her on her big night.
What is wrong with you, dude?
Okay, look, I may be pissed,
but that doesn't mean I did it.
What about her?
What?
You and Josh have been
at each other's throats
from the beginning.
That's true, yes.
We have a history, and I do hate him.
But guys, I'm your cox.
-I would never do this.
-And then there's Perry's gripe.
-Dude.
-What? What gripe?
I told you that in confidence, Noah.
What?
That is a 10.01 ash blond.
My base is also a 10.01 ash blond.
You stole my hair color, man.
-My mom picked it for me.
-But…
[Perry] It doesn't matter.
I didn't break the oar, I swear.
What about Cam? Wasn't he also pissed
about the whole stroke thing?
Wow. Thanks, man. What about you?
How do we know you don't have a grudge?
You've never given Josh a piggyback.
Well, yeah, not for lack of trying.
Why do you hate piggybacks, man?
I also have a reason to hate Josh.
Okay, I don't.
I just wanted to be included.
Who could hate this jawline?
Yeah, well, apparently everyone.
[Noah] I'm sorry,
but I'm going to state the obvious.
Ryder has been gunning for Josh
all season.
He swung at him at the clambake.
He got booted from stroke.
Their granddad came to watch the race.
-And Ryder wanted to sabotage Josh.
-Screw you, man.
You think I would tank the race
over some petty cousin drama?
[Perry] But it's not petty, is it?
One of you is going to get crowned
the king of Regis Airlines.
How could you stoop so low?
-I didn't do it!
-Let's search his bag!
-What the hell, Quaid?
-[Perry] Is the saw in there, Ryder?
-You have nothing to fear if innocent.
-No, go ahead. Search it. Fine.
It's not in there, Quaid.
Yeah. I know.
See?
And just for the record,
I don't want Josh to lose.
I wanna beat him.
In broad daylight. In front of everybody.
Do you believe him?
[clears throat] Well, one way to find out.
There's a security camera
pointed at the sheds.
The footage is on Coach's laptop.
It'll show us who got in.
One of you. Please, go jailbreak it.
[snaps]
-Great. Perry, go!
-[Perry] Me? Why?
I don't know how to hack a computer.
So youtube it!
-But there's so many ads.
-Dude!
-Okay, fine. I'll go pay for premium.
-[Teagan] Thank you.
And the rest of you, go. Look for the saw.
Noah and I
are going to process the evidence.
Go! Come on.
No.
-What are you doing?
-[Josh] Oh, uh, I'm looking for the saw.
Nothing yet,
but I did find an oyster shucker.
You're not here for the oyster shucker,
are you?
Who do you think we're gonna see
on security camera footage?
[Josh] The whole team?
[Teagan] Come on.
Who do you think did this?
Uh…
I mean, could be Baloo.
He's madder than I thought.
Could be Cam.
Cam? Why?
We kind of got into it this morning.
About what?
His sunglasses were broken.
Said he needed a new pair,
and he flipped out.
He has been on edge lately.
But it couldn't be Cam, could it?
Hm…
I mean, I guess it makes sense.
Yeah, Coach pulled Ryder,
but put you in stroke
when it should have been him. So…
[ominous music playing]
Wait. You think
Cam should be in stroke instead of me?
I didn't mean it like that.
No, it's okay. You can be honest with me.
Josh.
Well, yeah, he-he deserves it.
But how come?
Come on.
Okay, Cam puts the team first.
You know, no ego, no personal agenda.
He really pulls for the boat.
And I don't?
-Well…
-Is that how everyone sees me?
Even you?
I see that you're trying to prove
you're a different Josh.
So you think
I'm good enough to make out with,
but not good enough for stroke?
-I didn't mean that.
-Nah.
I think you did.
[comically intriguing music playing]
[bottles clattering]
Bunch of scofflaws.
[Teagan] Okay, where were we?
[bottles clatter]
-What's that?
-Quaid set up a speakeasy in the erg room.
The guys were out there partying
instead of looking for the saw.
So you confiscated it?
Actually, those are empties.
I'm helping them recycle.
Everyone hates my party.
Noah, come on. Your… Your party's fun.
Yeah, really? So given the choice
between a night at Quaid's bar
or a night at my murder mystery?
I'd do a murder mystery.
-Lies.
-It's… It's cool.
Okay? It's just,
you know, the wrong crowd.
Oh great. So now I can't read the room.
It's not that.
It's just we're not puzzle people.
The only thing we have in common is crew.
If we weren't in a boat together,
we probably wouldn't be friends.
Wow, you suck at pep talks.
Hey, but that's what's cool
about being a part of a team, you know?
You get to be exposed
to everybody's interesting interests.
And, um…
No, Noah, people who wouldn't be
your people become your people.
Just give it time.
Okay.
Besides, you are really fricking good
at this mystery stuff, okay? We need you.
If Perry can't figure out
the security camera footage,
we'll need to figure this out
ourselves, okay?
So… where are we?
[suspenseful music playing]
Okay. Well, Quaid and I
were stretching outside this morning.
Mm-hmm.
Perry and Crabby
were taking selfies in the erg room.
Mm-hmm.
Hold on.
What?
Cam said he was stretching
in the erg room before the race, right?
But this photo was taken in the erg room.
He's not in it.
Cam lied.
Hey.
No sign of the saw.
You know how you said you were
stretching in the erg room earlier?
Yeah.
Perry and Crabcatcher were too,
and, you know, they didn't see you.
Well, I was just in the corner. So.
Which corner?
Wait, you think I did it?
Yeah, I don't… I don't know, Cam.
I mean, you have been
acting different lately.
You walked out at the dance. No one knows
where you were during the sabotage.
-What am I supposed to think?
-That I'm the Cam you know.
The one who'd never sabotage the team.
Yeah, but the Cam I know
wouldn't pick a fight with Josh, either.
How did you know
I got in a fight with Josh?
We were the only people there.
He told me.
Right.
You guys are pretty close now, huh?
-We're not that close.
-Close enough that he's sharing.
You wanna know what I was doing?
I was selling my dad's truck
to one of the Westvale rowers.
-Cam. Why didn't you just tell me that?
-Because it's no one's business.
[melancholy music playing]
You really think I'd do this to him?
Yeah, you don't know me at all.
[Perry] Huddle up.
I'm in. And here we go.
Teagan did her morning checks.
Fast forward.
You didn't mention Josh was there too.
Uh, he was grabbing gear.
I needed tape and wrap.
Teagan's out 20 minutes later. So's Josh.
A long time to be grabbing gear.
My dad called.
Then there's a bunch of nothing…
-Well, guess we've seen enough.
-Wait, there's more.
Baloo?
You didn't mention going to the sheds.
That's a Westvale duffel bag.
Baloo, what are you doing
with a Westvale rower?
And what were you doing with him
in boat storage?
What do you think I was doing?
So Thirst Trap Guy's a Westvale rower.
You're dating the enemy.
[Perry] Hang on. There's more footage.
-You left him in there alone?
-[dramatic music playing]
[Noah] He has a bag.
Could have brought the saw,
cut the oar, and left.
I can't believe he did this.
["From a Different Life, It Seems"
by Alex Banin playing]
I can't believe you used me, Logan.
I thought we had something… real.
I'm an idiot.
Lose my number.
♪ Do you miss when
You would do whatever you would like? ♪
♪ Life is just so different ♪
♪ I don't miss it ♪
♪ But I miss you sometimes ♪
♪ And I never care no more ♪
♪ Just bought a one-way from New York ♪
♪ I'll come back when I can't afford you ♪
♪ Or I'm over it ♪
♪ I never care no more ♪
♪ Bought a one-way from New York ♪
♪ I'll come back when I can't afford you ♪
♪ Or I'm over it ♪
♪ You were setting fires, and I… ♪
Hey.
[all murmuring and comforting]
-♪ Don't do that anymore… ♪
-[phone buzzes]
♪ Don't do that anymore, anymore ♪
-♪ And I never care no more ♪
-[phone vibrating]
I can't.
Come here.
He's blocked.
-Thanks.
-Okay.
I just need a minute.
Hey, man.
The team wanted to send you
emotional support carbs.
Banana chocolate chunk. Your fave.
[Baloo] Leave me alone, Josh.
Hey, look, I know
you don't want to hear from me now,
but I have to tell you something.
I'm sorry.
For what?
Baloo, you've always been
such a good friend to me,
and you don't deserve any of this.
I, uh…
-[Baloo sniffles]
-I…
I can't make any of this better,
and I really wish I could.
[soft music playing]
My sister is my sister,
and I still think you're a piece of shit
for dumping her.
I'm glad we agree on something.
That was crazy. I can't believe
we solved a real-life mystery.
Yeah, I told you it wasn't me.
If it weren't for Teagan and Noah,
you would've kicked me off the team.
That was so intense, man. Also, sorry.
[team apologizing]
Oh… There's news afoot.
Today's rankings just came in.
Lakeview came third,
but Cedarside finished twelfth.
They're out!
We're going to the Haverford Cup.
-Yeah!
-[all cheering]
[Perry] You know what this calls for?
A murder mystery.
Noah, why don't you give us the next clue?
-Seriously?
-[Quaid] Yeah, man.
We can't just leave
a dowager murdered there.
Okay. Um, well, I'll give you a hint.
The oyster shucker
is not the real murder weapon.
And, and… the dowager duchess
isn't actually murdered.
-[Crabcatcher] What?
-[team gasps]
So she… faked her death?
[Cam] She could be
in cahoots with somebody.
[Perry] Cahoots. Good word.
[Teagan] Hm.
I'm guessing you didn't…
You didn't text me so we could pick up on
our make-out session from this morning?
No.
You know, you're right about me.
I, um… I don't do
what's best for the team.
Josh, I didn't mean for it
to come out harsh.
No. It's true though.
I'm selfish, and I hurt people.
Almost everyone had a motive against me.
Yeah, because everybody was in shock.
Okay? They were looking
for someone to blame.
Teagan.
You're not supposed to be with me.
What? Because I said
Cam should be in stroke?
-Because I'm-I'm not a good person.
-Josh.
Look, from the first day we met,
you thought I was an asshole.
-Yeah, but I don't think that anymore.
-Well, I'm not different.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Could you just be honest with me?
-Is that what you want? You want honesty?
-Yeah!
We're both on the rebound,
so let's just cut our losses.
Oh wow.
[somber music playing]
It's good to know how you really feel.
["Passenger" by Sir Chloe playing]
♪ I know I don't remember everything ♪
♪ My passenger, you take away my sleep ♪
♪ I soak my cigarettes in gasoline ♪
♪ I try, there's no relief
There's no relief ♪
♪ Ooh, what do I do? ♪
♪ It happened then
But I still have the wound ♪
♪ Ooh, it's no, no use ♪
♪ My passenger, you ruin my perfume ♪
[Cam] Maybe everything you have,
you don't deserve.
[phone ringing]
Hi, Dr. Monroe.
[Monroe] Josh, your ECG results came back.
Your left ventricle wall has thickened.
What does that mean?
You're going to need surgery.
Until then, no physical activity.
But I have a race today.
My family's watching.
Josh, you are at serious risk
of a heart attack.
Do you understand that?
[rushing sound swells]
♪ Ooh, what do I do? ♪
♪ It happened then
But I still have the wound ♪
♪ Ooh, it's no, no use ♪
♪ My passenger, you ruin my perfume ♪
[song ends]
[intriguing music playing]
[music ends]